indnav.com 2009-03-17

# Indnav.com - India Classifieds, Travel Guide, Tours, Tour Operators, Hotels, Maps and Properties in India.

| **Privacy Policy and Terms of Use

* * *

**  
---  
**Privacy Policy**  
  
Privacy issues are a high priority for us at Indnav and we follow standard industry practices to maintain your personal information. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

 **Indnav** does not spam or sell/lease its user information to third parties.  
  
****

**Policy Coverage**  
  
This Privacy Policy covers Indnav's treatment of personally identifiable information that Indnav collects when you are on the Indnav site, and when you use Indnav's services. This policy also covers Indnav's treatment of any personally identifiable information that Indnav's business partners share with Indnav. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Indnav does not own or control, or to people that Indnav does not employ or manage.  
****

**Personal Information Collected by Indnav**  
  
**ONLINE REGISTRATION:** In order to become an Indnav member, you must first create a member account on Indnav by providing information about yourself including but not limited to name, email address, country, city and a password. Only email address and password are required fields for all users except Tour Operators. For Tour Operators, email address, password, city, country, name of the company are the required fields and URL of your site is an optional field.  
  
**OPTIONAL PROFILE INFORMATION:** Once your provide the basic information to create an account, you will have the opportunity to provide additional information about yourself in the 'About Me' section under 'My Account'. Provision of this additional information beyond what is required at registration is entirely optional; it allows you to better identify yourself and create superior networking opportunities with other through shared contexts. It also enables you to better identify yourself and find new opportunities on Indnav. Your Profile information is visibile to all visiting the site.  
****

**Accessing and Changing Your Account Information**  
  
You can review the personal information you provided us and make any desired changes to the information, or to the settings for your Indnav account, at any time by logging in to your account on the Indnav website and editing the information on your 'About Me' page. You can also close your account on Indnav sending your request to member relations with your login email address. Your request will be processed within 7 business days  
****

**How is the information used?**  
  
We use your email address to send you:

  * Password reminder and registration confirmation
  * Special offers
  * News letters
  * Changes in the service's policy or terms of use
  * Event based communications such as order information, renewal notices, invites, reminders etc. 

****

**What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of your information?**  
  
Supplying personally identifiable information is entirely voluntary. You are not required to register with us in order to use our sites. However, we offer some services only to visitors who do register. 

You may change your interests at any time and may opt-in or opt-out of any marketing / promotional / newsletters mailings. Indnav.com reserves the right to send you certain service related communication, considered to be a part of your Indnav account without offering you the facility to opt-out. You may update your information and change your account settings at any time. 

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by emailing us at support@indnav.com to opt out.

 **Cookies**  
Indnav (or third party service providers on our behalf) may set and access cookies on your computer. A cookie is a small amount of data (often including a unique identifier), that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. Indnav uses cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our site.  

We may use cookies, IP address and browser data to control the display of ads, to deliver editorial content, and to personalize information. Our cookies may contain personally identifiable information.

Some of our advertisers may serve you cookies as well. We do not have control over cookies placed by advertisers. If you don't want cookies, most Web browsers include an option that allows you to not accept them. If you set your browser to refuse cookies, some portions of our sites may not function efficiently.  
  
****

**How can you correct inaccuracies in the information?**  
  
To correct or update any information you have provided, our sites allow you to do it online. In the event of loss of access you can email us at support@Indnav.com  
****

**How can you have your account deleted from Indnav?**  
  
In order to have your account deleted you can email us at support@Indnav.com  
****

**Use of Information by Indnav**  
  
Indnav is an online website that offers a variety of services designed to connect people from around the world. The information, whether personal information of any form of self-expression is used to help you describe yourself to other users. Indnav also collects additional information in order to operate and improve our service. Indnav, is the sole owner of the information collected on the Indnav site.

 **VISIBILITY OF PUBLIC CREATIVE CONTRIBUTIONS:** In addition to being a social and professional networking site, Indnav also provides a variety of forums for its members to express themselves in the form of articles, columns, opinions, comments, reviews, art and photographs. Since this expression is linked to the member's identity and the expression is in the public domain, the compilation of a member's creative contributions to Indnav will be visible to all visitors of Indnav whether or not they are registered members of Indnav.

 **EMAIL COMMUNICATIONS:** Indnav generally communicates with you as a registered member of Indnav through the primary email that you have specified at the time of registration. This is also used as the login text string in conjunction with the password to authenticate you on the Indnav site. Your email and password are never shared with anybody within or outside Indnav. Indnav uses this email address to send you three types of communications:

  * Sending you emails related to the proper functioning of your account (e.g. when you receive a response to a classified you have posted on Indnav or when you receive an invitation to join the personal network of another person)
  * Sending you newsletters that you have subscribed to
  * Sending you occasional announcements about changes in Indnav's policies or promotions introduction of new services
  * Please note that these email communications may contain commercial messages of advertisers; however, Indnav does not provide your personal information or emails to any of the advertisers; we just include the advertising banners they provide us in the emails that we send. As always you can opt out of the newsletters or promotional announcements.

****

**Other Terms of Use**  
  
****

**Policy on Abuse on Indnav**  
  
Indnav is committed to ensuring and enforcing a safe and friendly online community space for all our members. To this effect, we have come up with a Policy on Abuse that we would like all our members to be aware of. These rules govern the use of the Indnav.com website and its product/service offerings and we would like all our members to cooperate in complying with these rules so that everyone can have a pleasant experience.

 **Conduct and use of language:**

  * Member contributions must be civil and tasteful and must not be malicious or designed to offend. Use of swear-words or profanity is strictly prohibited.
  * Do not refer to the personality of other participants or attack an individual's character or personally insult another member. Do not use the Network to harass, threaten or verbally abuse or intimidate anyone, or behave in any manner that would cause annoyance or distress to other members.
  * Do not to post any material that is obscene, defamatory, profane, libelous, threatening, harassing, abusive, hateful or embarrassing towards other person(s) or an entity. We encourage a healthy exchange of opinions and disagreements. By all means challenge an opinion â€“ but please do it respectfully. Name-calling, insults and use of foul or abusive language will not be tolerated. This includes the use of offensive member Display Names and URLs (your personal website address on Indnav). 
  * Please be sure before you divulge the details of your identity or personal information in your post(s), including photos of yourself or your family and friends. Anything posted online is accessible to the entire internet community and Indnav.com is not liable in cases where such information is misused. Please be aware of the general dangers of online information sharing like identity theft, phishing and other fraudulent activites.
  * Members of Indnav.com are not permitted to collect or distribute personal data concerning other members at any time. 
  * Do not post messages more than once. This is also known as flooding. Indnav.com reserves right to delete such posts and may terminate the accounts of such members.
  * A member of Indnav.com must not impersonate another member.

****

**Changes to Privacy Policy and Notice**  
  
Indnav may change this policy from time to time in its discretion. Your continued use of our sites indicates your consent to this privacy policy and any amended versions of it. This policy was last updated on October 8th, 2008.
